MD MOSTAFIJUR RAHMAN

Flutter Developer



CONTACT INFORMATION

Male

fuadmostafij6@gmail.com

01798172012

GitHub

LinkedIn

Mirpur, Dhaka, Bangladesh

OBJECTIVE

A Professional Full Stack Mobile App Developer, A hard-working individual and the ability to communicate effectively in a team setting, and possesses a strong willingness to learn about entrepreneurship and business seek. To gain practical experience and express my innovative creative skills for self and company growth.

SKILLS

Language:

English, Bangla

Computer:

Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Programming:

Flutter, Dart, JavaScript, React.js, python basic, Django

EDUCATION

Feb 2018 - June 2022
Bangladesh University of Business & Technology,
B.Sc. in Computer Science Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/2022 - PRESENT
Flutter App Developer (Android and IOS)
Expert It Solution, Dhaka Bangladesh

ACTIVITIES

2018 - 2022BUBT IT Club, BUBT Robotics Club.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Strong organizational skills.

Mathematical aptitude.

Drive to keep up to date with developments and trends in the tech and modern media world.

The ability to learn quickly

The ability to interpret and follow technical plans

Problem-solving skills

Strong communication skills

PROJECT

- eBasket, Ecommerce App
- Job Univa, Find a Job
- Rio Live, Live Streaming App
- PiaraBazar E-commerce App
- Rebusel A Real State App